<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FitTracker</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="no_training_prompt">You Have No Trainings Saved. Do You Want To Add Your Routines First (Recommended)?</string>
    <string name="fitJournalExp">Here, You Can Log Your Training History.\n\nSimply:\n\n1)Choose A Date,\n\n2)Select The Training You Want To Input... If You Have No Trainings Saved,You Will Be Asked To Input Some. You Do Not Have To Follow This Step, You Can Also Add Freestyle Trainings (Trainings Without A Name, Just A Description And Difficulty). However, If You Do A Training Regularly, We Recommend Adding It First (See Trainings)\n\n3)If You Rested, Click The Green Button. If You Rested When You Should Not Have, Click The Red Button.\n\n4)Click The Add Button!
    </string>
    <string name="icon_exp_trainings">Once You Add A Training, It Will Be Displayed On The Calendar, With One Of These Icons, Based On Its Difficulty</string>
    <string name="weightJournalExp">Here You Can Log Your Weight For The Day.\n\nSimply:\n\n1)Chose A Date\n\n2)Enter Your Weight For The Selected Date\n\n3)You Are Done!\nThe App Will Do The Rest For You, And Make All The Calculations Neccessary For You To Know If You Are On The Right Path To Your Weight Goals</string>
    <string name="icon_exp_weight">Once You Add A Weight Entry, It Will Be Displayed On The Calendar, With One Of These Icons, Based On Its Weather Your Weight Changes Are Good Or Bad.\n\nOptimal Weight Maintenance Is Considered Anything Withing 0.5 KG If Your Ideal Weight.</string>
    <string name="communityExp">Our Community Is Where You Can Download Trainings From Other Users!\n\nSimply Enter The Community Page, And You Can Start Browsing Right Away.\n\nFeel Free To Search Trainings By Name Or Difficulty.\n\nYou Can Share Your Own Trainings With The FitTracker Community, From Your Trainings Page!</string>
    <string name="communityFurtherExp">Note: You Can Not Download A Training By A Name, That You Already Used In Your Own Trainings! If You Try To Do So, The App Will Ask You To Select A New Name For The Downloaded Training!</string>
    <string name="communityDownloadExp">To Download A Training,\nSimply:\n\n1)Select The Training You Want To Download\n\n2)Press This Button:</string>
    <string name="trainingPageExp">The Training Page Is Where You Can Add, Browse, Edit And Delete All Of Trainings, From One Place.\n\nAll Trainings Must Have 3 Things:\n1)A Name (The Name Must Be Unique)\n\n2)A Description: This Is Where You Should Enter Exactly What You Did In That Training. In Case You Are Planning To Share This Training With The FitTracker Community, We Recommend Being s Descriptive As Possible (Search UPPER1 OR LEGS1 For An Example Of A Perfectly Described Training)\n\n3)A Difficulty: To Categorise Trainings, We Have 3 Difficulties, Represented By 3 Colors:</string>
</resources>